Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG.42.5
New York University Archives
- Series II: Administrative Files, 1961-1988; 212471
  - Subseries D: Development, 1964-1980; 212472
    - William Brice -- Dinner, 1985 November-1987 March; 212905 (Box II:7, File 43)
    - William Brice -- Dispersal and Shipping, 1986 October-1987 January; 212904 (Box II:7, File 44)
    - Rick Horton -- Small Gallery Exhibition, 1986 December-1987 March; 212903 (Box II:7, File 45)
    - Harrisons -- Correspondence, 1985 April-1987 May; 212902 (Box II:7, File 46)
    - Harrison, Helen Mayer and Newton -- "Nobody Told Us When to Stop Thinking", 1987 March-October; 212901 (Box II:7, File 47)
    - Harrisons -- Loans and Condition, 1987 March-April; 212900 (Box II:7, File 48)
    - Paul Hunter -- White Noise (Small Gallery Exhibition), 212899 (Box II:7, File 49)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Correspondence, 1985 May-1987 September; 212898 (Box II:7, File 50)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Shipping, 1987 March-June; 212897 (Box II:7, File 51)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Jill Giegerich Return (Lannan Foundation), 1987 June; 212896 (Box II:7, File 52)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Insurance, 1987 February-May; 212895 (Box II:7, File 53)
    - Awards in the Visual Arts -- Miscellaneous, 1986 September-1987 September; 212894 (Box II:7, File 54)
    - Pat Keck (Small Gallery in Conj. AVA), 1987 March-1988 January; 212893 (Box II:7, File 55)
    - Pat Keck (Small Gallery in Conj. with AVA), 1987 April-June; 212892 (Box II:7, File 56)
    - Out of eastern Europe -- Correspondence, 1987 February-September; 212891 (Box II:7, File 57)
    - Out of Eastern Europe -- Contract, 1987 May; 212890 (Box II:7, File 58)
    - Out of Eastern Europe -- Shipping, 1987 May-August; 212889 (Box II:7, File 59)
    - Out of Eastern Europe -- Loan Agreement, 1987 May-August; 212888 (Box II:7, File 60)
    - Ricardo Zulueta -- Cintas Fellowship, 1988 March 1; 212887 (Box II:7, File 61)
    - Ricardo Estanislao Zulueta -- Tableau Utopia, 1987 June-August; 212886 (Box II:7, File 62)
    - Lee Gordon -- The Hooded Painting (Small Gallery Sept. 14-Oct. 24, 1987), 1987 August-October; 212885 (Box II:7, File 63)
    - Lee Gordon -- The Hooded Paintings (Small Gallery Sept. 14-Oct. 24, 1987), 1987 August-November; 212884 (Box II:7, File 64)
    - Morality Tales -- Correspondence, 1986 October-1989 January; 212883 (Box II:7, File 65)
    - Morality Tales -- Correspondence, 1987 May-August; 212882 (Box II:7, File 66)
    - Morality Tales -- NY Institute for the Humanities Talk (October 16), 1987 September 23; 212881 (Box II:7, File 67)
    - Morality Tales -- Video Project, 1987 October-November; 212880 (Box II:7, File 68)
    - Morality Tales -- Dinner, 1987 August-September; 212879 (Box II:7, File 69)
    - Morality Tales -- Tour Schedule, Circa 1986-1988; 212878 (Box II:7, File 70)
    - Morality Tales -- Shipping and Handling, 1987 August-October; 212877 (Box II:7, File 71)
    - Morality Tales -- Photograph Permissions, 1987 September-November; 212876 (Box II:7, File 72)
    - Morality Tales -- Contract, 1986 November 10; 212875 (Box II:7, File 73)
    - Morality Tales -- Insurance and Contract, 1986 November-1987 August; 212874 (Box II:7, File 74)
    - Juan Gonzalez (Window Installation in Conj. with Morality Tales), 1987 August-November; 212873 (Box II:7, File 75)
    - Jaar/Sheehan -- Correspondence, 1987 September-November; 212872 (Box II:7, File 76)
    - Jaar/Sheehan -- Loans, 1986 December-1987 April; 212871 (Box II:7, File 77)
    - Black Mountain College -- Correspondence, 1987 May-1988 March; 212870 (Box II:7, File 78)
    - Black Mountain Collage -- Shipping, 1987; 212869 (Box II:8, Folder 1)
    - Black Mountain College -- Shipping and Installation, 1987 January-1988 March; 212868 (Box II:8, Folder 2)
    - Black Mountain College -- Contract, 1986 June 5; 212867 (Box II:8, Folder 3)
    - Black Mountain College -- Loans, Insurance andn Facilities Reports, 1985 July-1988 January; 212866 (Box II:8, Folder 4)
    - Gaylen Gerber (Small Gallery), 1987 September-1988 June; 212865 (Box II:8, Folder 5)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- NEA and Related Miscellaneous, Undated; 212864 (Box II:8, Folder 6)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- Correspondence, 1985 October-1988 April; 212863 (Box II:8, Folder 7)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- Agreement, 1985 October-1986 December; 212862 (Box II:8, Folder 8)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc --Shipping, 1987 December-1988 March; 212861 (Box II:8, Folder 9)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- Insurance, 1976 July-1988 February; 212860 (Box II:8, Folder 10)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- Stained Glass from the Cloisters (Small Gallery), 1987 August-1988 March; 212859 (Box II:8, Folder 11)
    - Viollet-Le-Duc -- Stained Glass from the Cloisters (Small Gallery), 1987 December; 212858 (Box II:8, Folder 12)
    - Cecil Beaton -- HMC Proposal, 1987 August-September; 212857 (Box II:8, Folder 13)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Correspondence, 1986 September-1988 June; 212856 (Box II:8, Folder 14)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Invitation Lists, Undated; 212855 (Box II:8, Folder 15)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Mellor Lecture, 1988 March-April; 212854 (Box II:8, Folder 16)
    - Cecil Beaton -- London Materials, 1987 July-1988 February; 212853 (Box II:8, Folder 17)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Loans, Insurance and Shipping, 1988 January-May; 212852 (Box II:8, Folder 18)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Budget and Agreements, 1987 July-December; 212851 (Box II:8, Folder 19)
    - Cecil Beaton -- Miscellaneous, 1978 July-1988 March; 212850 (Box II:8, Folder 20)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Correspondence, 1986 November-1988 October; 212849 (Box II:8, Folder 21)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Contracts and Agreements, 1988 January-1990 October; 212848 (Box II:8, Folder 22)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Exhibition Tour, 1988 March-1989 April; 212847 (Box II:8, Folder 23)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Aids Support Organizations List, Circa 1988-1989; 212846 (Box II:8, Folder 24)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Installation and Condition, 1988-1990; 212845 (Box II:8, Folder 25)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Budget, 1987 September; 212844 (Box II:8, Folder 26)
    - Rosalind Solomon -- Shipping, Returns and Other Miscellaneous, 1988 May-1995 March; 212843 (Box II:8, Folder 27)
    - Eric Avery -- Works on Paper (Small Gallery), 1988 April-July; 212842 (Box II:8, Folder 28)
    - Twelve From New York -- The 1988 Selections From the Nordstern Collection, 1987 November-1988 October; 212841 (Box II:8, Folder 29)
    - Show and Tell -- Correspondence, 1981-1988; 212840 (Box II:8, Folder 30)
    - Show and Tell -- Budget, 1985; 212839 (Box II:8, Folder 31)
    - Show and Tell -- Financial and Other Miscellaneous, 1986 December; 212838 (Box II:8, Folder 32)
    - Show and Tell -- Lenders List, 1988 September-October; 212837 (Box II:8, Folder 33)
    - Show and Tell -- Institution Lenders (A-G), 1987 October-1989 January; 212836 (Box II:8, Folder 34)
    - Show and Tell -- Institution Lenders (N-Z), 1987 October-1988 November; 212835 (Box II:8, Folder 35)
    - Show and Tell -- Private Lenders, 1987 October-1988 November; 212834 (Box II:8, Folder 36)
    - Show and Tell -- Lenders, 1987 November-1988 November; 212833 (Box II:8, Folder 37)
    - Show and Tell -- Loan Rejections/Dropped, 1987 October-1988 March; 212832 (Box II:8, Folder 38)
    - Show and Tell -- Lenders and Other Miscellaneous, 1987 October-1988 November; 212831 (Box II:8, Folder 39)
    - Show and Tell -- Loans and Shipping, 1988 June-November; 212830 (Box II:8, Folder 40)
    - Show and Tell -- Shipping (Pick Up), 1988 July-October; 212829 (Box II:8, Folder 41)
    - Landmarks of NY -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Show and Tell), 212828 (Box II:8, Folder 42)
    - Landmarks of NY -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Show and Tell), 1988 August-September; 212827 (Box II:8, Folder 43)
    - Luc Courchesue -- Encyclopedia Chiaroscuro, 1985-1988, 212826 (Box II:8, Folder 44)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Correspondence, 1986 January-1989 February; 212825 (Box II:8, Folder 45)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Contract, 1988 May 23; 212824 (Box II:8, Folder 46)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Shipping, 1988 October-1989 May; 212823 (Box II:8, Folder 47)
    - Adolf Wolfli -- Invoices, 1988 October-November; 212822 (Box II:8, Folder 48)
    - Shelly Bachman -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Wolfli), 1988 October-1989 January; 212821 (Box II:8, Folder 49)
    - Michael Landy, 1989 January-October; 212820 (Box II:8, Folder 50)
    - French Revolution -- Proposed Exhibits (1 of 2), 1985-1988; 212819 (Box II:8, Folder 51)
    - French Revolution -- Proposed Exhibits (2 of 2), 1987; 212818 (Box II:8, Folder 52)
    - Politics and Polemics -- Correspondence, 1987 September-1989 March; 212817 (Box II:8, Folder 53)
    - Politics and Polemics -- February 11 Dinner, 1989 February; 212816 (Box II:8, Folder 54)
    - Politics and Polemics -- Contract, 1988 September-November; 212815 (Box II:8, Folder 55)
    - Poletics and Polemics -- Shipping, 1988 September-1989 June; 212814 (Box II:8, Folder 56)
    - Politics and Polemics -- NEH Proposal, 1987; 212813 (Box II:8, Folder 57)
    - Politics and Polemics -- Materials, 1985 June-1988 May; 212812 (Box II:9, Folder 1)
    - Masami Teraoka -- Small Gallery, 1988 January-1989 April; 212811 (Box II:9, Folder 2)
    - Masami Teraoka -- Small Gallery, 1988 January-1989 January; 212810 (Box II:9, Folder 3)
    - Andy Warhol -- Correspondence, 1986 May-1990 August; 212809 (Box II:9, Folder 4)
    - Andy Warhol -- NEH Proposal and Donna De Salvo Resume, 1986-1988; 212808 (Box II:9, Folder 5)
    - Andy Warhol -- Press Photos, Returns, Requests, 1989 January-1990 December; 212807 (Box II:9, Folder 6)
    - Andy Warhol -- Studio Museum/Pedestal, 1989 March-May; 212806 (Box II:9, Folder 7)
    - Andy Warhol -- Guest List, 1989 February; 212805 (Box II:9, Folder 8)
    - Andy Warhol -- Donna De Salvo Contract, 1988 February 3; 212804 (Box II:9, Folder 9)
    - Andy Warhol -- General Travel File, 1989 September-November; 212803 (Box II:9, Folder 10)
    - Andy Warhol -- Shipping/Ollendorff (1st Tour: Carnegie, Serpentine, ICA), Circa 1989-1990; 212802 (Box II:9, Folder 11)
    - Andy Warhol -- Dispersal (1 of 2), 1990 April-1991 January; 212801 (Box II:9, Folder 12)
    - Andy Warhol -- Dispersal (2 of 2), 1990 October; 212800 (Box II:9, Folder 13)
    - Andy Warhol -- Tour (ICA, Carnegie, Serpentine), 1989 April-July; 212799 (Box II:9, Folder 14)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (ICA, Philadelphia), 1989 April-1990 January; 212798 (Box II:9, Folder 15)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Carnegie Museum of Art), 1988 December-1989 November; 212797 (Box II:9, Folder 16)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Serpentine Gallery), 1989 January-1990 March; 212796 (Box II:9, Folder 17)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Foundation Cartier), 1989 December-1995 July; 212795 (Box II:9, Folder 18)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Newport Harbor Art Museum), 1989 September-1990 March; 212794 (Box II:9, Folder 19)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Lingotto, Turin), 1989 November-1990 October; 212793 (Box II:9, Folder 20)
    - Andy Warhol -- Traveling Venues (Shipping/Extended Tour to Newport ,Turin, Versailles), 1989 December-1990 October; 212792 (Box II:9, Folder 21)
    - Andy Warhol - Shipping ,Pickup and Returns of Objects Not Touring (February 1989), 1989 January-May; 212791 (Box II:9, Folder 22)
    - Andy Warhol -- Works Not Traveling to Newport, Lingotte, Cartier, 1989 November-December; 212790 (Box II:9, Folder 23)
    - Andy Warhol -- Works Not Traveling to Carnegie, Serpentine, ICA, 1988 December-1989; 212789 (Box II:9, Folder 24)
    - Andy Warhol -- Extended Loan List, Undated; 212788 (Box II:9, Folder 25)
    - Andy Warhol -- Loans(Rejections/Dropped), 1988 June-1989 December; 212787 (Box II:9, Folder 26)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lender Lists, Undated; 212786 (Box II:9, Folder 27)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (John Ardoin), 1988 July-1992 February; 212785 (Box II:9, Folder 28)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Alison Beyea), 1988 October-1990 December; 212784 (Box II:9, Folder 29)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Simeon Braguin), 1988 January-1989 December; 212783 (Box II:9, Folder 30)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Stephen Bruce), 1988 November-1989 July; 212782 (Box II:9, Folder 31)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Bruttal/Warhol Foundation), 1989 January-1990 July; 212781 (Box II:9, Folder 32)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (John Butler), 1988 October-1990 December; 212780 (Box II:9, Folder 33)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Johnston and Carnegie), 1988 July-1989 December; 212779 (Box II:9, Folder 34)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Alvin Chereskin), 1988 December-1990 December; 212778 (Box II:9, Folder 35)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Inman Cook), 1988 June-1990 December; 212777 (Box II:9, Folder 36)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Rainer Crone), 1989 April-1990 December; 212776 (Box II:9, Folder 37)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Anthony D'Offay Gallery, London), 1989 February-1990 December; 212775 (Box II:9, Folder 38)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Betty Lou Davis), 1988 December-1989 December; 212774 (Box II:9, Folder 39)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Mr. and Mrs. Arthur Edelman), 1988 December-1990 July; 212773 (Box II:9, Folder 40)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Findley-F.I.T.), 1989 March-May; 212772 (Box II:9, Folder 41)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Gene Federico), 1988 December-1990 December; 212771 (Box II:9, Folder 42)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Mr. and Mrs. Ronald Feldman), 1988 December-1990 December; 212770 (Box II:9, Folder 43)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Otto Fenn), 1988 December-1990 July; 212769 (Box II:9, Folder 44)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Steve Frankfurt), 1989 July-1990 July; 212768 (Box II:9, Folder 45)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Suzie Frankfurt), 1988 December-1989 May; 212767 (Box II:9, Folder 46)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Tina Fredericks), 1988 June-1990 July; 212766 (Box II:9, Folder 47)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Amy Gassner-Starks), 1988 December-1989 December; 212765 (Box II:9, Folder 48)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Jacqueline Gonnet), 1988 December-1989 December; 212764 (Box II:9, Folder 49)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Mr. and Mrs. Guillermo De Osma), 1988 August-1990 December; 212763 (Box II:9, Folder 50)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Alison B. Harwood), 1988 December-1989 June; 212762 (Box II:9, Folder 51)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Richard Holmes), 1988 September-1991 January; 212761 (Box II:9, Folder 52)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Art Kane), 1988 December-1989 December; 212760 (Box II:9, Folder 53)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Leonard Kessler), 1988 December-1990 December; 212759 (Box II:9, Folder 54)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (George Klauber), 1988 December-1990 December; 212758 (Box II:9, Folder 55)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Tom Lacy), 1988 December-1992 June; 212757 (Box II:9, Folder 56)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Kenneth J. Lane), 1988 December-1990 December; 212756 (Box II:9, Folder 57)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Kate Lloyd), 1989 February-1990 March; 212755 (Box II:9, Folder 58)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Christian Marclay), 1988 August-1991 January; 212754 (Box II:9, Folder 59)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Keith McCarthy), 1988 December-1991 January; 212753 (Box II:9, Folder 60)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Hopps/Menil Collection), 1989 January-December; 212752 (Box II:9, Folder 61)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Druesedow/Metropolitan Museum), 1989 January-May; 212751 (Box II:9, Folder 62)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Melissa Meyer), 1989 January-1990 December; 212750 (Box II:9, Folder 63)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Fritzie Miller), 1988 May-1989 May; 212749 (Box II:9, Folder 64)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Robert Miller Gallery), 1989 March-1990 December; 212748 (Box II:9, Folder 65)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Barbara Moore), 1988 December-1990 December; 212747 (Box II:9, Folder 66)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Gene Moore), 1989 February-1990 December; 212746 (Box II:9, Folder 67)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Mr. and Mrs. Robert Pliskin), 1988 August-1990 December; 212745 (Box II:9, Folder 68)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Radio Advertising Bureau), 1988 August-1991 January; 212744 (Box II:9, Folder 69)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Buddy Radisch), 1988 December-1989 May; 212743 (Box II:9, Folder 70)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Luigiano Rossi), 1988 December-1989 November; 212742 (Box II:9, Folder 71)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Mala Rubenstein), 1988 December-1990 July; 212741 (Box II:9, Folder 72)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Douglas Sackfield), 1989 January-1990 December; 212740 (Box II:9, Folder 73)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Schultz/Bert Greene Estate), 1988 June-1989 December; 212739 (Box II:9, Folder 74)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Babs Simpson), 1989 February-December; 212738 (Box II:9, Folder 75)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Frank Streich), 1988 December-1991 February; 212737 (Box II:9, Folder 76)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Tiffany and Co.), 1988 December-1989 December; 212736 (Box II:9, Folder 77)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (James Warhola), 1988 August-1990 December; 212735 (Box II:9, Folder 78)
    - Andy Warhol -- Lenders (Yale University Art Gallery), 1989 January-October; 212734 (Box II:9, Folder 79)
    - Andy Warhol -- Insurance Reports, 1989; 212733 (Box II:9, Folder 80)
    - Zuka -- The French Revolution Through American Eyes (Small Gallery), 1986 November-1989 February; 212732 (Box II:9, Folder 81)
    - Mike Bidlo (Window Installation in Conj. with Warhol Exhibit), 1989 February-September; 212731 (Box II:9, Folder 82)
    - Mike Bidlo (Window Installation in Conj. with Warhol Exhibition), 1989 March-September; 212730 (Box II:9, Folder 83)
    - Robert Morris -- NEH Proposal, Circa 1986-1988; 212729 (Box II:10, Folder 1)
    - Robert Morris -- Correspondence, 1986 July-1989 July; 212728 (Box II:10, Folder 2)
    - Robert Morris -- Dinner (5/22), 1989; 212727 (Box II:10, Folder 3)
    - Robert Morris -- Loans and Lender Lists, CIrca 1987-1989; 212726 (Box II:10, Folder 4)
    - Robert morris -- Lenders, 1988 June-1989 October; 212725 (Box II:10, Folder 5)
    - Robert Morris -- Shipping, 1988 May-1989 August; 212724 (Box II:10, Folder 6)
    - Bernard Frize -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Robert Morris), 1989 May-July; 212723 (Box II:10, Folder 7)
    - Weegee -- NEH Proposal, 1988-1989; 212722 (Box II:10, Folder 8)
    - Ching Ho Cheng -- Invitation List, Circa 1989; 212721 (Box II:10, Folder 10)
    - Ching Ho Cheng -- Lenders, 1989 August-1990 January; 212720 (Box II:10, Folder 11)
    - Excommunication -- Correspondence, 1989 August-November; 212719 (Box II:10, Folder 12)
    - Weegee -- Photographs/Framing, 1989 June-July; 212718 (Box II:10, Folder 9)
    - Excommunication -- Rick Bolton, 1989 October-1990 February; 212717 (Box II:10, Folder 13)
    - Excommunication -- Steve Evans, 1989 October-1990 January; 212716 (Box II:10, Folder 14)
    - Excommunication -- The Jewish Museum, 1989 October-1990 January; 212715 (Box II:10, Folder 15)
    - Excommunication -- Hillary Leone, 1989 October-1990 January; 212714 (Box II:10, Folder 16)
    - Excommunication -- Anthony Reynolds Gallery, 1989 October-1990 January; 212713 (Box II:10, Folder 17)
    - Excommunication -- Anthony Reynolds Gallery, 1989-1990 September; 212712 (Box II:10, Folder 18)
    - Excommunication -- Bernice Steinbaum Gallery, 1989 November-1990 January; 212711 (Box II:10, Folder 19)
    - Excommunication -- Mizra Tabrizian, 1989 September-1990 January; 212710 (Box II:10, Folder 20)
    - Excommunication -- Shipping, 1989 October-1991 February; 212709 (Box II:10, Folder 21)
    - Hujar -- Fundraising, Correspondence Lists and Other Miscellaneous, 1989 February-1991 June; 212708 (Box II:10, Folder 22)
    - Hujar -- Lenders, 1989 December-1991 February; 212707 (Box II:10, Folder 23)
    - Hujar -- Traveling Exhibition, 1990 June-1991 April; 212706 (Box II:10, Folder 24)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Correspondence, 1989 September-1990 June; 212705 (Box II:10, Folder 25)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Lannan Foundation Grant Application, 1987-1988; 212704 (Box II:10, Folder 26)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Conservation Treatment (1 of 2), 1990; 212703 (Box II:10, Folder 27)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Conservation Treatment (2 of 2), 1990; 212702 (Box II:10, Folder 28)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Shipping, 1990 February-May; 212701 (Box II:10, Folder 29)
    - Gerhard Richter -- The Saint Louis Art Museum Exhibition Contract, 1990 February; 212700 (Box II:10, Folder 30)
    - Gerhard Richter -- Symposium, 1990 February-May; 212699 (Box II:10, Folder 31)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Correspondence, 1989 July-1990 March; 212698 (Box II:10, Folder 32)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Graeme Murray Gallary/John Weber, Fidlay, Goldsworthy, Cooper, 1990 January-September; 212697 (Box II:10, Folder 33)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Helen Chadwick), 1990 April; 212696 (Box II:10, Folder 34)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Graeme Murray Gallery/John Weber, Findlay, Goldsworthy, Cooper), 1990 April-September; 212695 (Box II:10, Folder 35)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Lisson Gallery/John Virtue, Karshad), 1990 April-September; 212694 (Box II:10, Folder 36)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Louver Gallery NY/John Virtue, L.A. Louver), 1990 March-May; 212693 (Box II:10, Folder 37)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Joe McCrindle), 1990 April-July; 212692 (Box II:10, Folder 38)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Lenders (Richard Upton), 1990 March-June; 212691 (Box II:10, Folder 39)
    - Paysage Demoralise -- Landscape at the End of the Century (Shipping), 1990 March-1991 February; 212690 (Box II:10, Folder 40)
    - Peter Sebok -- Small Gallery (In Conj. with Paysage Demoralise), 1990 April-July; 212689 (Box II:10, Folder 41)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Akron Art Museum Correspondence, 1987 December-1988 July; 212688 (Box II:10, Folder 42)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Contemporary Art Museum, Houston Correspondence, 1988 August-1989 June; 212687 (Box II:10, Folder 43)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- General Correspondence, 1986 May-1991 April; 212686 (Box II:10, Folder 44)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Institute of Contemporary Art, Nagoya Correspondence (1 of 2), 1987 December-1990 November; 212685 (Box II:10, Folder 45)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Institute of Contemporary Art, Nagoya Correspondence (2 of 2), 1988 May-1991 May; 212684 (Box II:10, Folder 46)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- ICA, Tokyo General Correspondence, 1988 May-1990 May; 212683 (Box II:10, Folder 47)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- ISE Correspondence, 1987 July-1988 March; 212682 (Box II:10, Folder 48)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Japan Foundation Correspondence, 1983 September-1991 March; 212681 (Box II:10, Folder 49)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Japan-U.S. Friendship Correspondence, 1987 July-1988 March; 212680 (Box II:10, Folder 50)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- MIT Correspondence, 1986 November-1991 February; 212679 (Box II:10, Folder 51)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Nanjo Correspondence, 1988-1991; 212678 (Box II:10, Folder 52)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- National Museum of Art, Osaka Correspondence, 1987 February-1990 October; 212677 (Box II:10, Folder 53)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Other Possible Venues Correspondence, 1987 December-1988 October; 212676 (Box II:10, Folder 54)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- San Francisco MOMA Correspondence, 1987 December-1989 June; 212675 (Box II:10, Folder 55)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Seattle Art Museum Correspondence, 1988 March-1990 October; 212674 (Box II:10, Folder 56)
    - Against Nature (Japan) -- Tomiaki Yamamoto Correspondence, 1986 September-1987 September; 212673 (Box II:10, Folder 57)